Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
I can't hear you.
我听不到你说话。
Aye, aye, Captain!
是啊是啊，队长！
♪ Oh...
♪ 哦...
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he. ♪
♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ If nautical nonsense be
something you wish... ♪
♪ 如果航海方面的废话是
你想要的东西...♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish. ♪
♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通。 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ Ready?
SpongeBob SquarePants! ♪
♪ 准备好了吗？
海绵宝宝！ ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants!
♪ 海绵宝宝！
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Ah, observe the majesty
of the mighty iceberg.
啊，观察陛下
巨大的冰山。
This frozen giant,
这个冰冻的巨人，
normally found
floating in polar regions,
通常发现
漂浮在极地地区，
can sometimes stray
into warmer waters,
有时会迷失
进入温暖的水域，
causing dramatic changes
in climate
造成巨大的变化
在气候中
for tropical undersea life.
适合热带海底生物。
Yes, it seems Old Man Winter
paid us a visit late last night,
是的，看来是冬天老人
昨晚深夜来拜访我们，
and he brought with him
not a pillow or a sheet
他带来了
不是枕头或床单
but a blanket...
a blanket of snow!
但一条毯子...
一片雪！
Yes, from Jellyfish Fields...
是的，来自水母田……
to residential abodes...
到住宅区...
to bustling downtown...
到繁华的市中心...
it's nothing
but the white stuff.
没什么
但白色的东西。
Whoopee!
哎哟！
And local residents
are taking notice.
还有当地居民
正在注意。
Hmm...
唔...
Hey!
嘿！
What's this?
这是什么？
Drops of rain
frozen into ice crystals?
雨滴
冻结成冰晶？
I shall harness their energy
and rule the world!
我将利用他们的能量
并统治世界！
Aah... oh! Stop!
啊啊……哦！停止！
I wish to rule you!
我想统治你！
Snow angel!
雪天使！
Oh...
哦...
Hey!
嘿！
Thanks a lot, SpongeBob!
非常感谢，海绵宝宝！
While you were just
standing there whistling,
当你刚刚
站在那里吹口哨
someone threw a snowball at me!
有人向我扔雪球！
Oh, really, Patrick?
哦，真的吗，帕特里克？
Did the snowball look like this?
雪球是这样的吗？
Yeah.
是的。
This is serious, SpongeBob.
这很严重，海绵宝宝。
Someone's after me.
有人在追我。
I think I better leave town.
我想我最好离开这座城市。
Patrick, I threw it.
帕特里克，是我扔的。
We're having a snowball fight.
我们正在打雪仗。
Don't you get it?
你不明白吗？
Snowball fight?
打雪仗？
I want to play!
我想玩！
Well, first,
you have to make a snowball.
嗯，首先，
你必须做一个雪球。
Oh, yeah! A snowball.
哦，是啊！一个雪球。
Ooh, this is going to be great!
哦，这会很棒的！
Huh?
啊？
Wha...?
世界卫生大会...？
Aw...!
噢...！
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
Can you help me make a snowball?
你能帮我堆雪球吗？
Sure, pal.
当然，朋友。
Thanks, buddy.
谢谢，伙计。
Patrick!
帕特里克！
How could you?!
你怎么可以？！
It's a snowball fight, remember?
这是一场打雪仗，记得吗？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Ah, yes...
啊，是的...
Warm fire, cozy slippers,
温暖的炉火，舒适的拖鞋，
and a piping hot cup of tea
with a lemon wedge.
和一杯滚烫的茶
配柠檬角。
Aah!
啊啊！
Why do I even bother?
为什么我还要打扰？
Would you two
你们两个愿意吗
please keep it down?!
请小声点好吗？！
Squidward! You're just in time
to enlist in my army!
章鱼哥！你来得正是时候
加入我的军队！
Join me and together
we'll defeat the Pink Menace!
加入我并一起
我们会打败粉红威胁！
That's me!
这就是我！
You start off as a buck private,
你一开始是一名普通二等兵，
but with hard work, perhaps
you can rise through the ranks
但通过努力，也许
你可以晋升
and become a regular private!
并成为一名普通私人！
Thanks, but no, thanks,
Major Stupidity.
谢谢，但是不，谢谢，
主要的愚蠢。
You and General Nonsense
over there will have
to fight without me.
你和一般的废话
那边会有
没有我的情况下战斗。
Got 'em both.
两个都得到了。
Patrick, you fool!
帕特里克，你这个傻瓜！
This was over before it started!
这一切还没开始就已经结束了！
I will now consider your
unconditional surren...
我现在将考虑您的
无条件投降...
der.
der。
So, that's how he wants it
to go down.
所以，这就是他想要的
下去。
Ooh.
哦。
Ha! You missed me!
哈!你想念我了！
Ooh.
哦。
Score one for the boys
back home!
男子队得一分
回家吧！
Yes? Oh, Patrick.
是的？哦，帕特里克。
What an unpleasant surprise.
多么令人不愉快的惊喜啊。
Oh, boy, nothing like
a game of charades.
哦，男孩，没有什么比
猜谜游戏
I was trying to tell you
that I was choking on snow,
我试图告诉你
我被雪噎住了
but the snow melted
and turned into water
但雪融化了
并变成了水
and I drank all the water;
now I'm better.
我把水都喝光了；
现在我好多了。
Fascinating.
迷人。
Now, where was I?
现在，我在哪里？
What?
什么？
Can I use your bathroom?
我可以使用你的浴室吗？
Patrick, go use
your own bathroom.
帕特里克，去使用
你自己的浴室。
I won't make it.
Please?
我不会成功的。
请？
No.
不。
Please?
请？
No.
不。
Please?
请？
No.
不。
Please!
请！
Make it quick.
快点吧。
That's okay.
没关系。
Aha!
啊哈！
Aiding the enemy!
援助敌人！
I caught you Squidward!
我抓住你了，章鱼哥！
Look, SpongeBob, I was just...
听着，海绵宝宝，我只是……
SpongeBob! Oh!
海绵宝宝！哦！
Yay! Squidward's
on my side!
耶！章鱼哥的
在我这边！
I most certainly am not!
我绝对不是！
Then that means he's on my side!
那说明他是站在我这边的！
No, SpongeBob, I'm not
on your side either!
不，海绵宝宝，我不是
也站在你这边！
I'm on nobody's side.
我不站在任何人一边。
Snowball fights are
for immature children,
打雪仗是
对于尚未成熟的孩子来说，
and I will not stoop
to your level.
我不会弯腰
达到你的水平。
If you two want to knock
each other's brains out
with snowballs,
如果你们两个想敲门
彼此的脑子都出来了
带着雪球，
kindly leave me out of it.
请让我远离它。
SpongeBob, let's go knock
each other's brains out!
海绵宝宝，我们去敲门吧
彼此的脑子都出来了！
I'm ready!
我准备好了！
Hmm.
唔。
Okay, Patrick, it's out.
好吧，帕特里克，一切都结束了。
Now, there's something
I'd actually like to see.
现在，有件事
其实我很想看看
Nothing wrong with getting
a front-row seat, I suppose.
得到没有什么错
我想是前排座位。
Ah.
啊。
What's this?
这是什么？
Wha... I... No!
什...我...不！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
You're supposed to be knocking
each other's brains out!
你应该敲门
彼此的脑子都出来了！
We signed a peace treaty,
Squidward.
我们签署了和平条约，
章鱼哥。
You were right...
Fighting is for children.
你是对的...
打架是为了孩子。
No, no, I misled you,
it's for adults, too.
不不不，我误导你了
它也适合成人。
Give me that peace treaty!
把和平条约给我！
There! Let the war
continue.
那里！让战争
继续。
Squidward,
that wasn't
the peace treaty.
章鱼哥，
那不是
和平条约。
That was a copy
of the peace treaty.
那是一个副本
和平条约。
Look, you two are
giving up too easily.
瞧，你们两个是
太容易放弃。
Now, Patrick,
pretend I'm SpongeBob.
现在，帕特里克，
假装我是海绵宝宝。
And who am I?
而我是谁？
You're Patrick.
你是帕特里克。
Can I be Mr. Krabs?
我可以成为蟹老板吗？
No! Wait, why?
不！等等，为什么？
He's a good leader.
他是一个很好的领导者。
Would you butt out?!
你敢放屁吗？！
Hey, you can't talk
to Mr. Krabs
嘿，你不能说话
致蟹老板
like that, Squidward!
就这样，章鱼哥！
I'm SpongeBob! You're Patrick!
我是海绵宝宝！你是帕特里克！
Now, what are you going to do?
现在，你要做什么？
Patrick, why didn't
you hit SpongeBob?
帕特里克，为什么不呢？
你打海绵宝宝了吗？
You said you were SpongeBob.
你说你是海绵宝宝。
It's true!
这是真的！
Now, get back to work!
现在，回去工作吧！
Oh, boy. All right,
I can see where
this is going.
哦，男孩。好吧，
我可以看到哪里
这正在发生。
Let's just say
for all intents and purposes
就说吧
出于所有意图和目的
that I, Squidward, am now
part of this war. Now...
我，章鱼哥，现在
这场战争的一部分。现在...
Where's your fort?
你的堡垒在哪里？
I don't have one, okay? Now...
我没有，可以吗？现在...
You need a fort, Squidward.
你需要一座堡垒，章鱼哥。
Forts win wars, Squidward.
堡垒赢得战争，章鱼哥。
Okay, fine!
You want a fort?
好吧，好吧！
你想要一座堡垒吗？
There, there's
your fort! Now...
那里，那里有
你的堡垒！现在...
That fort's too small.
那个堡垒太小了。
It's okay, Patrick.
没关系，帕特里克。
It's just a demonstration.
Now...
这只是一个演示。
现在...
He's right, Squidward.
他是对的，章鱼哥。
That thing would
never protect you.
那东西会
永远不会保护你。
It's downright puny.
实在是太微不足道了。
Trust me, it's fine!
相信我，没问题！
See? It is too small.
看？它太小了。
Not if I crouch down!
如果我蹲下来就不会！
You didn't let me crouch down!
你不让我蹲下！
See? Down here,
I am perfectly...
看？下面，
我完全...
Exposed.
裸露。
Would you two please...
请你们两个...
stop throwing...
别扔了...
snowballs?!
雪球？！
Squidward returned fire!
章鱼哥还击！
Then it's war!
然后就是战争了！
No, no, wait, wait.
不，不，等等，等等。
I was just giving
a demonstration!
我只是在给予
示威！
All right, that's it!
好吧，就是这样！
You guys asked for it!
你们自找的！
I got him! Ha! I got him.
我抓到他了！哈!我抓住了他。
In your face, SpongeBob!
在你面前，海绵宝宝！
That was actually
kind of... exciting!
那实际上是
有点……令人兴奋！
Why, I've never felt so alive!
为什么，我从来没有感觉如此充满活力！
He got you good, SpongeBob!
他对你很好，海绵宝宝！
Ooh!
哦！
Take cover!
掩护！
Take that! I got you!
拿那个！我接到你了！
Yeah, oh, I got you!
是的，哦，我找到你了！
Oh, take that!
哦，拿那个！
Whoa, I got you that time!
哇哦，那一次我抓住了你！
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Incoming!
来袭！
Hey, SpongeBob.
嘿，海绵宝宝。
Yes, Patrick?
是的，帕特里克？
I think Squidward's
taking this really seriously.
我觉得是章鱼哥
非常认真地对待这件事。
That last one had
his clarinet in it!
最后一个有
他的单簧管在里面！
Hmm, looks like
it's time for Plan B.
嗯，看起来像
是时候实施 B 计划了。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
The snowballs
have stopped falling.
雪球
已经停止下降。
I better take advantage
of this momentary cease-fire.
我最好好好利用
暂时的停火。
What?! My left flank is exposed!
什么？！我的左胁暴露了！
That bloated starfish is
going to run right through me!
那个浮肿的海星是
会直接穿过我的身体！
I'll just fix that right now.
我现在就解决这个问题。
Wait, that makes my north wall
a weak spot. Ha!
等等，这就是我的北墙
一个弱点。哈!
Here we go. Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
开始了。嗯嗯，嗯嗯。
Oh, oh, oh!
哦，哦，哦！
But if they attack
from the rear, I'm a goner.
但如果他们攻击
从后面看，我已经完蛋了。
There. Ha-ha!
那里。哈哈！
But what about the possibility
of an aerial attack?
但有什么可能性
空袭？
I guess that ought to do it.
我想应该可以做到。
Fort Squidward is now
all but impenetrable!
章鱼堡现在是
几乎是坚不可摧的！
Now, where are those fools?
现在，那些傻瓜在哪里？
Ha! The first shot
has been fired!
哈!第一枪
已被解雇！
Take this, Patrick!
拿着这个，帕特里克！
Taste my frozen fury!
尝尝我冰冻的愤怒吧！
Victory is mine!
胜利是我的！
Whee!
哎哟！
I got you now!
我现在找到你了！
Did you hear something, Patrick?
你听到什么了吗，帕特里克？
Nope.
没有。
Ah, a yard sale.
啊，庭院旧货出售。
You know the old saying:
你知道那句老话：
"One man's trash is
another man's treasure."
“一个人的垃圾是
另一个人的宝藏。”
Disposable?!
一次性的？！
Phooey.
噗。
For Mr. Krabs,
all trash is treasure.
对于蟹老板来说，
所有的垃圾都是宝藏。
Open for business.
开门营业。
See anything you like?
看看有什么你喜欢的吗？
Give you $1.50
for this umbrella.
给你 1.50 美元
为了这把伞。
$1.50 for that?!
1.50 美元？！
But it's an antique!
但这是古董！
It belonged to a queen.
它属于一位女王。
Ten bucks.
十块钱。
Ten bucks?!
十块钱？！
It's full of holes!
浑身都是坑啊！
It was the queen of Switzerland.
那是瑞士女王。
A queen, you say? That's...
你说女王？那是...
Wait a second,
they don't have a queen.
等一下，
他们没有女王。
Okay,
Mr. Bargain Hunter.
好吧，
讨价还价猎人先生。
Five bucks.
五块钱。
Deal!
交易！
Ah, the sweet smell
of an all-day sucker.
啊，甜甜的味道
一个整天傻瓜的人。
They taste even better.
它们味道更好。
Hi, Mr. Krabs.
嗨，蟹老板。
What you doing?
你在做什么？
I'm having an antique sale.
我正在举办一场古董拍卖会。
Have a look around.
看看周围。
Hey, Patrick,
look at this thing.
嘿，帕特里克，
看看这个东西。
Pretty cool, huh?
很酷吧？
That looks like
the toilet plunger
I threw out yesterday.
看起来像
马桶柱塞
我昨天扔了。
That ain't no toilet plunger.
那不是厕所柱塞。
This here's an antique!
这是古董！
It, uh... um... uh...
a 17th-century soup ladle, see?
它，呃……呃……呃……
17世纪的汤勺，看到了吗？
Man, was I using mine wrong.
伙计，我是不是用错了。
How much?
多少？
Five bucks.
五块钱。
I've only got seven.
我只有七个。
Deal!
交易！
Patrick Star,
you are one smart shopper.
帕特里克·斯塔,
您是一位聪明的购物者。
Wow! Look at this neat-o
soda-drinking hat.
哇！看看这个整洁的o
喝苏打水的帽子。
Oh! It must've belonged to
someone who was number one.
哦！它一定是属于
排名第一的人。
There's only been
a handful of number ones
只曾有过
少数几个数字
in the entire history
of forever.
在整个历史上
的永远。
That's right, SpongeBob,
and you're one of 'em.
没错，海绵宝宝，
而你就是其中之一。
Really?
真的吗？
This hat says
"Hey, I'm number one
这顶帽子说
“嘿，我是第一名
and I let gravity
do my drinking."
我让重力
帮我喝酒。”
This hat was made for you, boy.
这顶帽子是为你量身定做的，孩子。
You were born to wear this hat!
你生来就该戴这顶帽子！
Eee... ooh...!
哎呀……噢……！
A perfect fit, eh, son?
完美契合，嗯，儿子？
Oh, thank you,
Mr. Krabs!
哦，谢谢你，
蟹老板！
Thank you for
bringing us together!
谢谢你
让我们走到一起！
How can I ever repay you?
我该如何报答你呢？
With ten dollars.
带着十块钱。
All I have is five.
我只有五个。
Well, I guess it's no deal.
嗯，我想这没什么好说的。
I'll be right back.
我马上回来。
Ah!
啊!
Mr. Krabs,
I found 68 cents.
蟹老板先生，
我找到了 68 美分。
But maybe you could
take the other $4.32
但也许你可以
剩下的 4.32 美元
out of my paycheck.
从我的薪水中扣除。
What do you say?
你怎么说？
Well... I don't know...
嗯...我不知道...
Uh... okay!
呃……好吧！
But only 'cause you look
so dashing in that hat.
但只是因为你看起来
戴上那顶帽子是如此潇洒。
Thanks, Mr. Krabs!
谢谢蟹老板！
Don't mention it, boys!
别提了，孩子们！
What a couple of rubes.
真是一对乡巴佬。
Excuse me, sir, but are you
对不起，先生，您是吗？
the purveyor
of this curio stand?
供应商
这个古玩摊？
Yes, I am.
我是。
I understand you're selling
我知道你在卖
this rare novelty drink hat.
这顶罕见的新奇饮料帽。
Fresh out.
新鲜出炉。
Let me explain.
让我解释一下。
I'm prepared to give you
$500 for that drink hat.
我准备给你
那顶饮料帽 500 美元。
Fi-fi-fi-fi-fi...
菲菲菲菲菲菲...
Not so fast.
没那么快。
I'll give you $1,000
for such a hat.
我给你 1,000 美元
对于这样一顶帽子。
I'll give you
我给你
$100,000 in cash for said hat.
购买这顶帽子需要 10 万美元现金。
Sir, I'll give you
a million dollars for that hat!
先生，我给你
那顶帽子一百万美元！
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
There he is
with me million-dollar hat.
他在那里
和我一起价值百万美元的帽子。
I got to get it back
我得把它拿回来
before he finds out
how much it's worth.
在他发现之前
它值多少钱。
Ah! My bubble production
has increased twofold.
啊! My bubble production
Thanks to you, Hatty.
谢谢你，哈蒂。
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
Mr. K! How's the antique biz
treating you?
K先生！古董生意怎么样
治疗你？
Never mind that.
Listen...
没关系。
听...
I didn't want to say this
in front of Patrick.
我本来不想说这个
在帕特里克面前。
That hat makes you look
like a girl.
那顶帽子让你看起来
像个女孩。
Am I a pretty girl?
我是一个漂亮的女孩吗？
Oh, well, um...
哦，好吧，嗯...
You're...
you're beautiful.
你是...
你很漂亮。
Uh... heh-heh.
呃……呵呵。
All right, now give
me the hat back.
好吧，现在给
我把帽子还回来。
But, Mr. Krabs,
you said it yourself...
但是，蟹老板，
你自己说的...
I was born to wear this hat.
我生来就是为了戴这顶帽子的。
I don't want to give it back.
我不想还给它。
I can't part with this hat now.
我现在离不开这顶帽子。
Not after all
we've been through.
终究不是
我们已经经历过了。
Thanks, Mr. Krabs!
谢谢蟹老板！
I'll call you Hatty.
我就叫你哈蒂吧。
And that's when you showed up.
就在那时你出现了。
Aw, forget it!
哎呀，算了！
And you're not beautiful either.
而且你也不漂亮。
I'm not?
我不是吗？
SpongeBob, just the man
I wanted to see.
海绵宝宝，就是那个男人
我想看看。
Still playing with
that dumb old hat, eh?
还在玩
那顶愚蠢的老帽子，嗯？
Yep.
是的。
Not sick of that
boring old hat yet?
不厌倦那个
无聊的老帽子了吗？
Nope.
没有。
Not tired
不累
of that old piece of junk?
那个旧垃圾？
Uh-uh.
呃呃。
Not even a teensy, tiny bit?
哪怕一点点也没有？
Nope.
没有。
Then I guess
那我猜
you don't want to see
what's in my bag.
你不想看到
我的包里有什么。
What is it?
它是什么？
Novelty hats.
新奇的帽子。
How about this
air-conditioned one?
这个怎么样
有空调的吗？
Seems a little dangerous.
看起来有点危险。
The Juicer?
榨汁机？
Ooh...
哦...
Foxy Grandpa?
狐狸爷爷？
So, what do you say?
那么，你说呢？
Your silly hat
for all these hats.
你的傻帽子
对于所有这些帽子。
No deal, Mr. Krabs.
没有交易，蟹老板。
I'm sticking with Hatty.
我还是坚持哈蒂。
Thanks for the offer, though.
不过还是谢谢你的提议。
I thought the Foxy Grandpa
would get him for sure.
我以为是狐狸爷爷
肯定会得到他的。
I didn't want to have to do this
我不想这样做
but he leaves me
no other option.
但他离开了我
没有其他选择。
I'm going to have to
scare it off of him.
我将不得不
吓跑他。
This'll scare him.
这会吓到他的。
Oh, my gosh!
哦，天哪！
A floating shopping list!
浮动购物清单！
I'm not a shopping list...
我不是购物清单...
I'm a ghost...!
我是鬼……！
Now, listen, SpongeBob.
现在，听着，海绵宝宝。
How do you know my name?
你怎么知道我的名字？
Who are you?!
你是谁？！
I am the Ghost
of Soda Drink Hats.
我是幽灵
的苏打饮料帽子。
And I'm here to tell you
我来这里是为了告诉你
that that soda drink hat
you possess is cursed.
那顶苏打饮料帽子
你拥有的是被诅咒的。
Cursed?
被诅咒了？
Yes! It once belonged
to some guy who's dead now.
是的！它曾经属于
给某个现在已经死了的人。
What guy?
什么人？
Uh... Smitty something.
呃... Smitty 的东西。
Smitty what?
斯密蒂什么？
Uh, Smitty... Werben...
呃，斯密蒂……韦本……
Jaegerman... Jensen.
耶格曼……詹森。
He must have been number one.
他一定是第一名。
Number one in Bogeyland!
柏忌之地第一名！
Now, listen...
现在，听...
a curse will descend on you
诅咒将降临在你身上
unless the hat is returned
to its owner immediately.
除非帽子被退回
立即交给它的主人。
Immediately?
立即地？
Immediately...
立即地...
To its owner?
给它的主人？
Yes...
是的...
Right now?
现在？
Yes, yes!
是的，是的！
It must be returned
to its owner right now!
必须归还
现在就交给它的主人吧！
Hey, Mr. Krabs.
嘿，蟹老板。
Ahh! SpongeBob!
啊！海绵宝宝！
Uh, uh, what are you doing here?
呃，呃，你在这里做什么？
I was returning
the cursed soda drink hat
我正在回来
被诅咒的苏打饮料帽子
to its original owner:
Smitty Werben Jaegerman Jensen.
致其原始所有者：
斯米蒂·沃本·耶格曼·詹森。
What? There is
no Smitty Werben
Jaegerman Jensen.
什么？有
没有 Smitty Werben
耶格曼·詹森.
Sure there is!
当然有！
He's buried out
in Floater's Cemetery.
他被埋没了
在浮者墓地。
How did? I just...
怎么样？我只是...
You did... I would...
你会...我会...
Give me that shovel!
把那把铲子给我！
It was his hat Mr. Krabs.
这是他的帽子，蟹老板。
He was number one!
他是第一！
Huh?!
啊？！
Ahh!
啊！
Hold yourself together, Krabs.
蟹蟹们，振作起来。
It's just a boneyard...
filled with bones.
这只是一个坟场...
充满了骨头。
Ahh!
啊！
What's that?
那是什么？
It's Squidward.
这是章鱼哥。
What's he doing here?
他在这里做什么？
Ohh...
哦...
"Here lie Squidward's
hopes and dreams."
“这里躺着章鱼哥的
希望和梦想。”
What a baby. Where was I?
真是个宝贝啊。我当时在哪儿？
Oh, yeah! Gotta find
Smitty Whatsajipster.
哦，是啊！一定要找到
斯密蒂·Whatsajipster。
Nope... nope... no... no...
不……不……不……不……
No... uh-uh... no... no...
uh-uh... nope, not there...
不……呃呃……不……不……
呃呃……不，不在那里……
I've checked every headstone
in this cemetery
我检查了每一个墓碑
在这个墓地里
and there's no
Smitty Wabbablabba buried here.
并且没有
斯米蒂·瓦巴拉巴 (Smitty Wabbablabba) 埋葬于此。
Think, Krabs.
想一想，蟹蟹们。
Maybe something SpongeBob said
will give you a clue.
也许海绵宝宝说过的话
会给你一个线索。
Remember, licking doorknobs
记住，舔门把手
is illegal on other planets.
在其他星球上是非法的。
No, not that!
不，不是那样！
You'll never guess
你绝对猜不到
what I found in
my sock last night.
我发现了什么
我昨晚的袜子。
Go ahead, guess!
来吧，猜猜看！
No! No! No! No! No!
不！不！不！不！不！
It was his hat, Mr. Krabs.
这是他的帽子，蟹老板。
He was number one!
他是第一！
Ahh! Barnacles!
啊！藤壶！
I'll never find...
我永远找不到...
The grave!
坟墓！
Am I really going to defile
this grave for money?
我真的要玷污吗
这座坟是为了钱吗？
Of course I am!
我当然是！
Jackpot!
大奖！
Ooh. It's beautiful.
哦。很美丽。
Come to Papa.
来找爸爸吧。
Huh?
啊？
Come on, Smitty, let go.
来吧，斯密蒂，放手。
Rest in pieces, Smitty.
安息吧，斯密蒂。
I got the million-dollar hat!
我拿到了价值百万美元的帽子！
Hey, man, that's my hat.
嘿，伙计，那是我的帽子。
Give it back.
把它还给我。
What? No way.
什么？决不。
Just crawl back
into your hole, bone boy.
就爬回来
进你的洞里吧，骨头男孩。
Go ahead, play dead.
来吧，装死吧。
I guess I'm going to have
to take it from you.
我想我将会有
从你手中夺走它。
Yeah, right. You and what army?
是的，对。你和什么军队？
Only the army
of the living dead.
只有军队
活死人的。
Oh, no! I've seen this
on the late show.
哦，不！我见过这个
在晚间节目中。
You ghoulish fiends hold me down
你们这些残忍的恶魔压制着我
and take turns
nibbling on my innards.
并轮流
啃咬我的内脏。
Then you eat my brain and
leave my body for the buzzards.
然后你吃掉我的大脑然后
把我的身体留给秃鹰吧。
That's disgusting.
太恶心了。
We just want the hat back.
我们只想拿回帽子。
No flipping way!
没有翻转方式！
Back up! Back up, I say!
备份！后退，我说！
Attack.
攻击。
Tallyho!
塔利霍！
Look at me, I'm Errol Fin!
看着我，我是埃罗尔·芬！
You're falling apart,
marrow brain!
你快崩溃了，
骨髓脑！
You must be kidding!
你一定是在开玩笑！
Back to oblivion!
回到遗忘！
Hup-ho! How's your sister?
呵呵！你姐姐怎么样了？
All right, boneheads,
playtime's over.
好吧，笨蛋，
游戏时间结束了。
Yee-hoo!
呀呼！
Wa-ha!
哇哈！
A million dollars.
一百万美元。
I've got a million dollars!
我有一百万美元了！
Oh, there you are.
哦，你来了。
Well, I got it.
嗯，我明白了。
The rare novelty soda drink hat.
罕见的新奇苏打饮料帽子。
Let's start the bidding
at $1 million.
让我们开始竞价吧
100万美元。
Yeah, you want that all at once?
是的，你想一下子就得到这些吗？
A million dollars!
一百万美元！
You got to be kidding!
你一定是在开玩笑吧！
Hey! The poor sap's
not kidding.
嘿！可怜的闷棍
不是开玩笑。
Didn't you hear?
你没听到吗？
They found a whole
warehouse full of them.
他们发现了一整
仓库里装满了它们。
They're worthless!
他们一文不值！
Let's give Mr. Krabs a big hand!
让我们向蟹老板先生伸出援手吧！
Now, that's worth
a million dollars!
现在，这值得
一百万美元！
Hey, kid, wait up!
嘿，孩子，等等！
I saw him first!
我先看见他了！
I'll give you $1 billion!
我给你10亿美元！
Well, that's a spirit breaker.
嗯，这真是一个精神破坏者。
What a baby.
真是个宝贝啊。
Captioning sponsored by THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION
字幕由 THE 赞助
美国教育部
and NICKELODEON
和尼克国际儿童频道
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org
标题为
WGBH 媒体访问小组
访问.wgbh.org